Monster Family is a animation, family, fantasy film directed by Holger Tappe.
The Wishbone family are far from happy.
In an attempt to reconnect as a family, they plan a fun night out.
However, the plan backfires when they are cursed and all turned into Monsters.
Emma Wishbone (voice), played by Emily Watson.
Frank Wishbone (voice), played by Nick Frost.
Fay Wishbone (voice), played by Jessica Brown Findlay.
Max Wishbone (voice), played by Ethan Rouse.
Dracula (voice), played by Jason Isaacs.
Baba Yaga (voice), played by Catherine Tate.
Monster Family (also known as Happy Family in Germany) is a 2017 animated monster comedy film directed by Holger
Tappe, and written by David Safier and Catharina Junk, based on Safier's 2011 novel Happy Family.
The film stars Emily Watson, Nick Frost, Jessica Brown Findlay,
Celia Imrie, Catherine Tate, and Jason Isaacs.
The film received generally negative reviews from critics, and was a
commercial failure, grossing $26 million against a $30 million budget.
A sequel titled Monster Family 2 was released in 2021.
The tone is lighthearted.